I think the biggest thing
is just recognizing that
we're going to have AI forever.
like there's no getting away
from any of that we really
need to find a way to
harness the power that it has
to make us more like
effective and efficient
you don't know how to use
it you're going to fall
behind that being said if
that's all you use you're
useless because anyone can use AI
these are the three questions we'll talk
about.
So kind of keep these in mind while we're
going through.
Like an experience where
use of AI has helped
you learn something or
has been productive.
A time when it's felt uneasy,
unproductive, or crippling.
Maybe that's an extreme word,
but I'm having trouble
thinking of a synonym.
Then what kind of lab culture would you
support establishing any specifics?
In this instance, AI
was able to run a test
for me and collect data.
This will be very helpful because it can
run 24 So Tim's on at Claude, can you pick
up, move, run the following Google Cloud
code, post here the
results, and then return
the enclosure.
So it's giving it this code here.
And Claude took 42 minutes, picked it up,
sensor test ran, went down mid
like, if I had an e -bike,
I know myself well enough
that I would probably start
relying on the e -bike
intensively rather than
getting a workout that I need
every day, And so it's so
much easier to be complacent
when the tool is there.
not like we can choose to
not buy the e -bike right
it's the yeah it's like the
e -bike is there yes and
And like, oh, sorry, I bought it.
Yeah, I bought it for all this.
I literally bought it for everybody.
And the question I ask is,
how important is it for
us as students going into
the professional world soon
to be competent in not
only using AI, but using AI
fruitfully,
But, you know, he uses
his AI Jarvis to also,
you know, be his tool to,
you know, be there to run
the tests that he already
worked out or to support
his reasoning or stuff like that.
So kind of like that way
where Jarvis is a support
to Tony Stark and not
doing Tony Stark's work.
It relates a lot to how we've
learned things in general,
like all through school,
we taught how to do math,
and only after you understand
how to do that, then
you get to calculate